原创翻译  双语字幕
最新连载海外影视剧下载
仅供交流学习  禁止商用盈利
请登陆 www.YYeTs.com
翻译     C·A  苏小黛  Carolingo  feip
翻译     王木木  海云生  kathy567  glida
校对     布塔
时间轴
后期     渔夫
总监     布塔
勒贝尔的险招
冒风险  占先机
家族仪式  哎呦  秘密议会
急急如律令
急急如律令  勒贝尔的险招
亚历克斯  这边
Alex, this way!
快来
Come on!
快点
Hurry.
进去  别出来
Get in and don't come out.
丹尼尔  我害怕
Daniel, I'm scared.
嘘
Shh.
求你了丹尼尔  他们要杀了我
Daniel, please. They're trying to kill me.
请救救我  丹尼尔  求你了
Please help me, Daniel, please.
他在这里
He's in here.
不不不  老天  不要
No, no, no! God, no!
不  查尔斯  住手
No, Charles! Stop!
-海琳  -不要啊  住手
- Helene! - No, please, stop it!
不  查尔斯
No! Charles!
不  不
No. No.
查尔斯
Charles.
不  求你们了  住手
No, please. Please, stop.
不  你们没必要这么做
Please. No. You don't have to do this.
丹尼尔  我真为你骄傲
Daniel, I'm so proud of you.
求你们听...
Please, listen to...
你们不必这么做  什么都不会发生
You don't have to do this. Nothing's gonna happen.
海琳  海琳  求你劝劝他们
Helene! Helene, please just talk to them.
海琳
Helene!
不要啊  不要啊
Please, no! No! No, please!
不要啊
No!
勒多马斯
三十年后
长相厮守
To have and to hold.
从今以后
From this day forward.
无论福祸
For better, for worse.
富裕或贫穷
For richer, for poorer.
健康或病苦
In sickness, and in health.
至死不渝
Till death do us part.
即使你的家族比上帝还富有
And even though your family is richer than God,
吓得我心生怯意
intimidates the hell out of me...
你爸绝对讨厌我
your dad definitely hates me,
而你的酒鬼哥哥总是对我献殷勤
and your alcoholic brother keeps hitting on me...
老实说  我迫不及待想加入
I honestly can't wait to be a part
你这个略显操蛋的家庭了
of your moderately fucked-up family.
"略显"  这么说太给面子了
"Moderately"? That's pretty generous.
我靠
Holy shit!
你看起来真美
You look perfect.
你在干什么
What're you doing?
你在抽烟  在我原来的房间里
You smoking? In my old room?
给我
Give me that.
我们应该下去了
We should get down there.
你爸看起来像是在参加葬礼
Your dad looks like he's at a funeral.
-他讨厌我  -不  他不讨厌你  格蕾丝
- He hates me. - No. He doesn't hate you, Grace.
他觉得我是看上了你的钱
He thinks I'm after your money.
那是也是真的
Well, I mean, that's true.
-你只是要耐心点...  -太刻薄了
- You just gotta give it time... - So mean!
什么  不  那是真的
What? No, it's true.
宝贝  耐心点  好吗
Honey, just give it time. Okay?
-好  -好吗  我们太突然了
- Okay. - Okay? We sprung this on them.
-嗯  -他们习惯了三年的求爱期
- Yeah. - They're used to a three-year courtship.
我们可不是这样的
And not what we did.
我们是多久  一年半的...
The, I don't know, 18-month...
滚床单长跑
Bone-a-thon.
"滚床单长跑"  好吧
"Bone-a-thon"? Okay. Yeah.
-我们应该把它写进誓言里  -我写了
- We should put that in the vows. - I did.
很好
Oh, good.
再说谁在乎他们怎么想  他们都令人厌恶
Anyway, who cares what they think? They're horrible people.
我在乎他们的想法
Well, I-I care what they think.
因为他们是我爱的人的家人
Because they are the family of the man that I love.
我想让他们接受我
And I want them to accept me.
你还好吗  因为我已经够紧张了
Are you okay? 'Cause I'm nervous enough as it is.
不  不是那样的  我只是
No, it's not that. I just...
没有你  我...
Without you, I'm...
自家人
One of us.
-丹尼尔  -他们派我来接你
- Daniel. - I've been sent to fetch you.
♪ 这个新郎吓得尿裤子了 ♪
♪ Here comes the groom shitting his pants ♪
♪ 他简直不敢相信 ♪
♪ He cannot believe ♪
♪ 他的一生就这样完了 ♪
♪ That his entire life is over ♪
丹尼尔  混蛋  别闹了
Daniel, you fuck. Stop it.
我要放手了  三  二  放手
I'm gonna let you go in three, two... release.
别激动
Take it easy.
现在逃跑还来得及
It's not too late to flee, you know.
你不属于这个家庭
You don't belong in this family.
我这是在夸奖你
I mean that as a compliment.
好吧  如果你下定决心要做勒多马斯家的人
Okay. Well, if you're still determined to be a Le Domas,
那你们就该出去了  好吗
then would you please get yourselves outside. Okay?
恭喜啊  你个混蛋
Congratulations, you fuckface.
谢谢
Thank you.
我都不敢相信在半个小时后
I can't believe that in half an hour...
我就会加入勒多马斯游戏的
I will be a part of the Le Domas gaming...
王朝  帝国
dynasty? Empire?
"统治"  我们喜欢用"统治"
"Dominion." We prefer "dominion."
-"统治"  -是的  但是...
- "Dominion." - Yeah. But...
丹尼尔说得对
You know, Daniel's right.
我们可以  离开
We could just... leave.
是啊  "谢谢大家的礼物  都滚吧"
Sure, yeah. "Thanks for the presents. Go fuck yourselves."
不  我是认真的  我说真的  宝贝
No. I'm serious, I'm serious, honey.
我给你个离开的机会
I'm giving you an out.
就现在
Right now.
不了  谢谢  我毫无保留地加入
No, thank you. I'm all the way in.
你准备好了没
Are you ready for this?
靠  当然没
Oh, fuck no.
准备好了没
请笑一笑
Smile, please.
他可以找个更好的
He could've done so much better.
你这样说是因为他是你的最爱
You're just saying that because he's your favorite.
别这样  我爱你们所有人  平等地
Oh, please. I love all of you... equally.
两年是很长的一段时间  亚历克斯
Two years is a long time, Alex.
我开始觉得我们真的失去你了
I started to think we'd really lost you.
笑一笑  请笑一笑
Smile. Smile, please.
越自然越好
The more natural the better.
好的  很好
Okay, that's good.
别往心里去
Don't take it personally.
他们只是想知道你是不是拜金婊子
They're just trying to figure out if you're a gold-digging whore.
就像我老婆一样
You know, like my wife.
向左转
To the left.
她够漂亮了
She's pretty enough,
挺符合"廉价酒吧一夜情"
in a "last call at the dive bar" kinda way.
但她永远不会成为我们中的一员
But she'll never be one of us.
当然不会  亲爱的
Of course not, dear.
她有良知
She has a soul.
你姐姐在哪
Where the hell's your sister?
肯定是菲奇的错
I'm sure it's Fitch's fault.
他是个废物  但他是我们中的一员
He's useless. But he's one of us.
格蕾丝是吗
Is Grace?
你在这里啊
There you are.
你好
Hi!
Hi.
-帮个忙  -好的
- Give me a hand. - Oh. Okay.
很漂亮的盒子
It's a beautiful case.
谢谢夸奖  是我母亲的
Thank you. It was my mother's.
你抽烟吗
Do you smoke?
不抽
Oh, no.
紧张吗
Nervous?
因为你的血统不够高贵吗
Because your blood isn't blue enough?
他们也这样说过我
They said the same thing about me.
真的吗
They did?
抬头挺胸别理他们
Stand tall and fuck 'em.
最重要的是亚历克斯的想法
The only thing that matters is what Alex thinks.
而他的想法我们都知道
And that we know.
-我爱你  -我爱你
- I love you. - I love you.
我沾东西了吗
I have something?
见鬼
Oh, shit.
你还记得今天发生了什么吗
Do you remember anything that happened today?
一片模糊
It's a goddamn blur.
但我非常确定...
But I'm pretty sure...
-我们结婚了吗  -我们结婚了
- Did we get married? - We got married.
你是我老婆吗
Are you my wife?
-我靠  我靠  -是的  你是我老公
- Holy shit. Holy fucking shit. - Yes. You're my husband!
我的天  靠  宝贝
Oh, my God. Shit. Oh, babe.
宝贝
Babe.
穿着这个真麻烦
It's hard with this thing.
-我知道  听着  -抱着我
- I know. Listen. - Hold me.
我得告诉你...
I have to tell you something...
闭嘴  把裤子脱了
Shut up. Take your pants off.
不  我得告诉你一件事
No, I have to tell you something.
-格蕾丝  亲爱的  -我要帮你脱了
- Grace, honey. - I'm taking 'em off.
我操  操  有人
Holy shit! Holy shit. Someone's here.
什么
What?
天啊  海琳姑妈  能让我们单独待一会吗
Jesus, Aunt Helene! Can you give us a minute?
你们得藏得更好点才行
You'll have to hide better than that.
我们没他妈藏  明摆着的
We're not fucking hiding, obviously.
大家都等着呢
Everyone is waiting.
知道了  我们马上就下去
Yeah, we'll be down in a few minutes.
-抱歉  宝贝  -刚才那是什么鬼
- I'm sorry, honey. - What the hell was that?
那是我姑妈海琳
That's my aunt Helene.
她...她不太懂什么叫界限
She has, um... well, she has boundary issues.
看出来了
Yeah.
你们当然会有暗门
Of course you have a secret door.
这是仆人的过道
It's a servant's corridor.
贯穿整栋房子
They run all through the house.
抱歉  谁在等着呢
Sorry, who's waiting?
我刚才就是想跟你说这事
That's what I was trying to tell you. Um...
是这样  午夜的时候你得玩个游戏
So, at midnight you have to play a game.
这是有新人加入我们家时的传统
It's just something we do when someone new joins the family.
-游戏  -是的
- A game? - Yeah.
什么游戏
What game?
我不知道  就是  你要抽一张牌
I don't know. Uh, you draw a card.
据我所知可能是双陆棋  槌球  跳棋
Could be backgammon, croquet, checkers, for all I know.
我知道  我懂  挺傻的
I know. I know. It's stupid.
有点怪
It's a little weird.
为什么要玩游戏
Why, exactly?
可能因为我们是靠游戏发家的吧
I guess, because we made our money in games,
这是加入仪式的一部分
it's part of the initiation.
-我需要赢吗  -不  你只是得参加
- Do I have to win? - No. You just... you just have to play.
-然后...  -然后你...
- And then... - And then you...
你就正式成为家里的一员了
you are officially part of the family.
说真的  这对他们来说比婚礼还重要
Honestly, it means more to them than the wedding itself.
-就这事吗  -是的  就这事
- That's it? - Yeah, that's it.
我知道很荒唐
I know it's ridiculous.
只是一种奇怪的家族仪式
It's just a weird family ritual.
我们只要做一次就行  好吗
And we only have to do it once. All right?
好吧
Okay.
-好  -好
- Yeah. - Okay.
如果这能让你的家人接受我
If it gets your family to accept me,
我会好好下一把跳棋
I will play the shit out... of checkers.
-我很擅长的  -好
- I'm really good at it. - Okay.
好吧  你去帮我拖个十分钟
Okay. You go buy me ten minutes
我得摆出玩游戏的架势
'cause I gotta put on... my game face.
我看懂了  非常棒
I see what you did there. Very good.
好  那我在楼下等你  音乐室
Okay. So, uh, I'll meet you downstairs. Music room.
当然  家里有音乐室简直太正常了
Yes. A totally normal room to have in a house.
反正...就在楼下
Just... It is just downstairs.
右手边第二个房间
It's your second door on the right.
好的
Okay.
我就知道能在这里找到你
I thought I might find you here.
勒贝尔先生今天一定会与我们同在
I'm sure Mr. Le Bail is with us today.
你跟她说了多少
So, how much have you told her?
什么也没说  我不会说的
Nothing. And I never will.
明天我们就走了
Tomorrow we're gone.
如果她抽出了那张牌
If she pulls that card,
你准备好做必要之事了吗
are you prepared to do what's necessary?
家族仪式  秘密议会  勒贝尔的险招
日出
抱歉  不管你想说什么  请继续
Excuse me, whatever you wanna say, get on with it please.
你最好快点  午夜之前赶过来
You better hurry your ass up and get here before midnight.
收到消息给我回电话
Call me when you get this message.
多拉  再来两杯  谢谢
Dora, two more, please.
格蕾丝  亲爱的
Grace, darling.
-你的誓言写得真美  -谢谢
- Your vows were beautiful. - Oh. Thank you.
亚历克斯没告诉我们你是在寄养家庭长大的
Alex didn't tell us you were brought up in foster homes.
其实他现在什么也不告诉我们了  喝香槟吗
Not that he tells us anything these days. Champagne?
好的  谢谢
Thank you. Thanks.
我的养父母是很好的人
My foster parents were great people.
你懂的  他们尽了全力给我最好的
And, you know, they did what they could.
但那终究不能长久
But it was always temporary.
我总是梦想着能拥有一个家庭
I always sort of dreamed of having a... a family.
我知道亚历克斯一定很乐意一直未婚同居下去
I mean, I'm sure Alex would've loved living in sin forever.
我毫不怀疑
I don't doubt it.
但他  他真的理解
But he, um, he really understood
我有多看重...
how important it was for me to...
最终拥有一个真正的  永远的家庭
finally have a real, permanent family.
我只是不想让你们失望
And I just don't wanna let you down.
格蕾丝  我第一次见你时就跟托尼说过
Grace. When I first saw you, I said to Tony:
"咱们总算有个孩子带回来一个像样的"
"Finally. One of our children has brought home a good one."
你不知道我们有多感激
And you don't know how grateful we are
你把亚历克斯带回了我们身边
that you brought Alex back to us.
但是拜托
But please...
试着让他回到我们身边
try to bring him back into the fold.
我们是他的家人
We're his family.
我保证
I promise.
亲爱的
Sweetheart.
我就知道你会的
I knew you would.
妈  我先把她拐走一会  好吗
Mom, I'm just gonna steal her away. Okay?
她跟你说了什么
What'd she say to you?
她人真好
She's so sweet.
她说什么了吗
Did she say anything?
没有
No. No.
好吧
All right.
你没事吧  出什么事了吗
Are you okay? Did something happen?
没事  没有
Yeah, no.
我只是  我不太舒服
I just, I don't feel very well.
要是你想躺一会
Well, if you wanna lie down,
我们明天再玩那游戏不行吗
can't we just play the game tomorrow?
-不  不行  必须是今晚  -举起手来
- No, no, it has to be tonight. - Hands up!
杀杀杀杀杀
Kill, kill, kill! Kill, kill, kill!
抓住他  乔治
Get him, Georgie!
我们赶过来了  爸爸
Whoo! We made it, Daddy.
面具摘了  马上
Take it off, now!
-爸爸  -你尽管继续玩  伙计
- Daddy? - You just keep on playing there, buddy.
你太紧张了
You're so tense.
-勒贝尔会抓到你的  -混蛋
- Le Bail's gonna get you. - Asshole.
杀  杀  勒贝尔先生
Kill, kill! Mr. Le Bail!
你  穿白裙的女士
You. Lady in white.
瞧瞧  你一定就是新娘了
Look at this, you must be the bride.
-你好  -我是菲奇·布莱德利
- Hi. - Fitch Bradley.
我叫格蕾丝
Grace.
幸会
Pleasure.
-亚历克斯  -菲奇  你好吗
- Alex. - Hi, Fitch. How are you?
干得漂亮  抱歉我们卡在点上才来
Well done. Sorry we cut it so close.
今早  我们平时用的包机
We couldn't get our regular charter
没法离开戴高乐机场
out of de Gaulle this morning.
我可受不了再乘民航了  你懂吧
And I cannot fly commercial anymore, right?
-民航太糟了  你懂的  -格蕾丝
- It's the worst. You understand. - Grace!
我是艾米丽
I'm Emilie.
天啊  你的裙子太美了
Oh, my God, your dress is amazing!
我一直在图享网上偷偷关注你
I've been totally stalking you on Instagram.
是吗  这真是...
Oh, really? That's...
我们一定会成为最好的朋友
We're gonna be best friends.
很高兴见到你
Hi. Nice to see you.
我很激动要成为你们家的一员了
I'm so excited to be a part of your family.
我也是  我也是
Me too, me too!
那得由他决定  亲爱的
He will decide that, my dear.
海琳姑妈  真高兴见到你
Aunt Helene. It's nice to see you.
棕发侄女
Brown-haired niece.
你还存在着呢
You continue to exist.
女士们先生们  11:55了
Ladies and gentlemen, it is 11:55.
这会让你大开眼界的
This is gonna blow your mind.
好吧
Okay.
这个房间是仅限家里人使用的
So this room is reserved for family members only.
你先请  亲爱的
After you, my dear.
我的天
Holy shit.
曾祖父很喜欢玩他的游戏
Great-Grandfather enjoyed his games.
勒多马斯
格蕾丝
Grace.
维克多·勒多马斯
请坐
Have a seat.
你喜欢玩游戏吗
Do you like to play games?
那得看是什么游戏了
I guess it depends on what we're playing.
我们马上就会知道了
Well, we'll know in a moment.
我想你已经注意到了  我们家很看重传统
I gather you've noticed our family is big on tradition.
现在  现在到了你跟我们
And now, well, now the time has come
一起遵守这些传统的时候了
for you to join us in those traditions.
要讲故事了
Story time.
你可能知道  我的曾祖父  维克多
As you may know, my great-grandfather, Victor,
在内战期间开了一家不起眼的印刷店
set up a modest printing shop during the Civil War,
制作纸牌
manufacturing playing cards.
一代人以后
A generation later,
我的祖父把生意扩大到了体育用品和桌上游戏
my grandfather expanded into sporting goods and board games.
在我的领导下  勒多马斯家族游戏
Under my leadership, Le Domas Family Games
获得了四支职业体育团队的加盟
acquired four professional sports teams
更上了一层楼
and reached, well, even greater heights.
有人可能说这只是运气
Some may call it luck,
但运气不足以形容我们
but, well, it's a little more than that.
我们简直是被眷顾的
You know, it's almost as if someone's watching over us.
这一切都归功于一位极其慷慨的捐助者
It all began with a very generous benefactor.
以及这个盒子
And this box.
曾祖父原本是商船上的一名水手
You see, originally, Great-Grandfather was a merchant seaman.
生活很艰难
It was a hard life.
和很多人一样  他不想止步于此
And, like so many, he wanted more.
一次他出海航行的时候
On one of his many excursions abroad,
曾祖父遇到了勒贝尔先生
Great-Grandfather came to meet a Mr. Le Bail.
他是  他是船上的一名乘客
He was a... He was a passenger aboard the ship.
算是个收藏家
A collector, of sorts.
他会买下异国文物然后转卖给美国的富人
Purchasing exotic antiquities to resell to wealthy Americans.
当他们发现彼此都热衷于赌局时
After discovering a mutual passion for games of chance,
他们花了很多时间打牌
they passed a great many hours playing cards.
勒贝尔先生的其中一样收藏品就是
And among Mr. Le Bail's possessions was...
那个盒子
that box.
一天晚上
And one evening,
在喝了太多朗姆酒以后
after indulging in more than their fair ration of rum...
勒贝尔先生下了一个赌注
Mr. Le Bail proposed a wager.
如果曾祖父能在靠岸前
If Great-Grandfather could solve the mystery of the box
解开这个盒子的谜题
before arriving at port,
勒贝尔先生就会资助祖父想做的任何生意
Mr. Le Bail would finance any endeavor of Grandfather's choosing.
于是
Well...
曾祖父在海上花了很长时间
Great-Grandfather whiled away
研究这个盒子
the long hours at sea studying the box.
直到最后...
Until finally...
从那时起
And since that time...
每当有新人
whenever the Le Domases are presented
要加入勒多马斯家族的时候
with a new addition to the family...
我们就会在盒子里放一张空白的纸牌
we place a blank playing card into the box.
我们的新人则有抽牌的特权
Our initiate then has the privilege of drawing the card,
然后勒贝尔先生会告诉我们该玩哪种游戏
and Mr. Le Bail will tell us which game to play.
我抽到了象棋
I got chess.
玩法类似抽鬼牌
我抽到了老姑娘
I got Old Maid.
说真的  老姑娘是个什么玩意儿
Seriously, what the fuck is Old Maid?
菲奇
Fitch...
我只要抽牌就行了吗
So I just take out the card?
亲爱的  轮到你了
My dear, it is your turn.
上面写的什么  孩子
What does it say, girl?
上面写的
It says...
捉迷藏
It says, "hide and seek."
我们真的要玩这个吗
Are we really gonna play that?
有问题吗
Everything okay?
没事  没事  这是游戏规则
Yeah. Yeah. Those are the rules.
就玩捉迷藏  对吗  爸爸
Hide and seek, right, Dad?
是的  没错
Yes, indeed.
这是游戏规则
Those are the rules.
好吧  那谁捉谁藏呢
Okay, so, uh, who... who hides and who seeks?
鉴于你是新人  亲爱的
Well, it's your initiation, my dear.
你来藏
You get to be the one to, uh, to hide.
当然
Of course.
会很好玩的  亲爱的
This is gonna be fun, honey.
到我房间去等我  好吗
Yeah, just come meet me in my room, okay?
-不  我想认真玩  -我知道
- No, I wanna play for real. This is so weird. - No, no. I know.
那么  敬...勒贝尔先生
So, to Mister... Le Bail.
敬勒贝尔先生
To Mr. Le Bail.
-敬勒贝尔先生  -敬勒贝尔先生
- To Mr. Le Bail. - To Mr. Le Bail.
规则很简单
The rules are simple.
你可以躲在房子里的任何地方
You can hide anywhere inside the house.
我们会数到一百  然后试图...找到你
We then count to 100 and try to, um... well, find you.
你们不觉得这对我不太公平吗
Well, don't you think you have a little bit of an advantage?
不不  我们从不用摄像头
No, no. We never use the cameras.
我们一直都是
We always play the games
像在曾祖父那个年代一样玩游戏
as they would've been played in Great-Grandfather's time.
一直都是
Always.
我是不可能赢的  对吗
So, there's no way for me to win, right?
你可以一直躲到黎明
Well, you could, I mean, stay hidden till dawn.
-不了  谢谢  -不用
- No, thank you. - No.
你一离开这里
We're gonna start the count
我们就会开始计数  好吗
just as soon as you leave, okay?
好
Okay.
格蕾丝  祝你好运
Grace, good luck.
谁想玩个游戏
Who wants to play a game?
该玩捉迷藏啦
It's time for hide and seek.
♪ 跑  跑  跑 ♪
♪ Run, run, run ♪
♪ 跑去藏起来 ♪
♪ Time to run and hide ♪
♪ 跑  跑  跑 ♪
♪ Run, run, run ♪
《失乐园》第一卷
"在这里我们可以稳坐江山
"Here we may reign secure...
♪ 我会找到你 ♪
♪ And now I'm going to find you ♪
按照我的选择
and in my choyce
在地狱里一展宏图"
to reign is worth ambition..."
♪ 快呀  我在你身后 ♪
♪ Hurry, I'm behind you ♪
♪ 别  出  声 ♪
♪ Don't you speak ♪
♪ 捉  迷  藏 ♪
♪ Hide and seek ♪
♪ 溜进地窖或者爬进床底 ♪
♪ Tiptoe to the cellar or crawl under your bed ♪
♪ 无论你逃到哪里 ♪
♪ Anywhere you've fled ♪
♪ 我会找到你 ♪
♪ I am going to find you ♪
♪ 躲进阴影里 ♪
♪ Stay inside the shadows ♪
♪ 男孩女孩们 ♪
♪ All you girls and boys ♪
♪ 千万别出声 ♪
♪ Don't you make a noise ♪
♪ 不然我会找到你 ♪
♪ Or I am going to find you ♪
♪ 跑  跑  跑 ♪
♪ Run, run, run ♪
♪ 悄悄靠近猎物 ♪
♪ Creep up on my prey ♪
♪ 跑  跑  跑 ♪
♪ Run, run, run ♪
♪ 夜晚悄悄溜走 ♪
♪ Stalk the night away ♪
♪ 你可以跑进夜色 ♪
♪ You can scuttle off into the night ♪
♪ 但你身后会是谁 ♪
♪ But what will be behind you ♪
♪ 别  出  声 ♪
♪ Don't you speak ♪
♪ 捉  迷  藏 ♪
♪ Hide and seek ♪
♪ 像煎锅里的青蛙 ♪
♪ Like the frog inside a skillet ♪
♪ 平底锅里的龙虾 ♪
♪ The lobster in a pan ♪
♪ 你不知道我会找到你 ♪
♪ You don't understand that I am going to find you ♪
♪ 静止如山 ♪
♪ Be still as a mountain ♪
♪ 静默如鼠 ♪
♪ And quiet as a mouse ♪
托尼  这他妈是什么  哪年的古董啊
Tony, what the hell is this? How old is this thing?
♪ 我一定会找到你 ♪
♪ And I will surely find you ♪
♪ 滴  滴  答 ♪
♪ Tick, tick, tock ♪
♪ 你准备好了没 ♪
♪ Are you ready or not ♪
♪ 滴  滴  答 ♪
♪ Tick, tick, tock ♪
♪ 听着指针走 ♪
♪ Listen to the clock ♪
♪ 快跑进黑暗中 ♪
♪ Hasten off into the black ♪
♪ 别浪费下一秒 ♪
♪ Don't waste another heartbeat ♪
♪ 别  偷  看 ♪
♪ Don't you peek ♪
♪ 捉  迷  藏 ♪
♪ Hide and seek ♪
开始倒数吧
Let the countdown begin.
♪ 十  九  八 ♪
♪ Ten, nine, eight ♪
♪ 七  六  五 ♪
♪ Seven, six, five ♪
♪ 四  三  二  一 ♪
♪ Four, three, two, one ♪
准备好了没  我来了
Ready or not, here I come.
宝贝  也许你应该留在这里
Sweetheart, maybe you should just stay here.
看住房门
Watch the door.
谢谢  夏丽蒂
Thank you, Charity.
你的新婚之夜怎么样  格蕾丝
So, how was your wedding night, Grace?
棒极了  非常棒  我...
It was just great. Just great. I, uh...
我坐在升降机里
I sat in a dumbwaiter.
亚历克斯  亲爱的  我陪你一会儿好吗
Alex, honey, do you want some company?
我操
Fuck me.
这要玩多久
How long is this gonna take?
一般要多久
How long does this usually take?
这游戏没有一般可言
There is nothing usual about this.
我加入这个家族以来也只玩过一次
It's only happened once since I joined the family.
你们都默认我会用这玩意儿吗
Am I really supposed to know how to use this thing?
这样吧
You know what?
我要去休息一下
I'm just gonna make a quick pit stop.
我一紧张就闹肚子
I've got a nervous stomach.
你知道我从来都看不上你  对吧
You know I've never liked you, right?
好吧
All right.
我受够了
That's enough of this.
妈的
Shit.
Oh, shit.
乔治
Georgie.
-对不起  -天呐
- I'm sorry. I'm sorry. - Jesus.
-我差点吓尿了  -我知道
- I nearly pissed myself. - I know.
-你得仔细听我说  -乔治
- You need to listen to me very carefully. - Georgie.
-嘘  跟我来  -等下  我们在干什么
- Shh. Come with me. - Wait. What are we doing?
-蹲下  把你的裙子拽过来  -行  天呐
- Get down. Grab your dress, grab your dress. - Okay. Jesus.
乔治  我知道你在这儿
Georgie, I know you're in here.
乔...
Georg...
在这儿  她在这儿  快过来
Over here! Over here, over here!
各位  我找到她了
Guys, I found her!
我做到了
I did it!
爸爸  我做到了  快看
Dad! Daddy, I did it! Look!
爸爸  快来看我...
Daddy, come see what I mean...
糟了  糟了
Shit. Shit. Shit. Shit.
老天啊
Jesus Christ.
这是克莱拉
This is Clara.
她看起来像是穿着巨大的
Does she look like she's wearing a giant,
白色婚纱吗  艾米丽
white wedding dress, Emilie?
你为什么直接爆头  亲爱的
Why did you shoot her in the face, sweetheart?
你本该打残她
You're supposed to maim her.
为了仪式她得活着
She needs to be alive for the ritual.
我也不知道
I don't know.
-我听到了枪响  -是啊
- I heard a shot. - Yeah.
如果她死了  这算数吗
Well, if she dies, does this count?
当然不算  必须得是新娘
Of course it does not count. It must be the bride.
那我们现在怎么办
Well, what do we do now?
我不知道  让我想想
Well, I don't know. I'm... I'm thinking.
克莱拉
Clara, hey.
会没事的
It's gonna be okay.
丹尼尔  你能不能...
Daniel, could you?
好了  我们去走走
Come on, let's take a walk.
她会死的  各位
She's gonna die, guys.
走吧
Walk it off.
我们要怎么处理她
So, what do we do with her?
把她挪走  不能让格蕾丝看到
Move her. We don't want Grace to see.
把提灯给我
Give me the fucking lanterns.
好了  选吧
Okay. Call it.
-正面  -你选对了
- Heads. - Heads it is.
-你来抬腿  -好的
- You get the legs. - Okay.
慢着
Hold on.
要滑下去了  好了  好  走吧
It's slipping. Yeah, good. Oh, good. Okay. Go.
我最喜欢她了
She was my favorite.
在这等着  别动
Wait here. Don't move.
好了  亲爱的  你得站起来
Okay, sweetie, you gotta get up.
我们得赶紧把你弄出去
We gotta get you out of here right now.
来  站起来  就这样
Okay. Stand up, here we go.
拿好你的手机  带上钥匙
Okay. Okay, grab... grab your phone. Grab the keys.
操  糟了
Fuck. Shit.
一定是斯蒂文斯把手机拿走了...
Okay. Stevens must've taken the phone, so...
-亚历克斯  怎么回事  -你得逃跑  懂吗
- Alex, what the fuck? - You're gonna have to run, okay?
捉迷藏  你抽到了唯一一张坏牌
Hide and seek. You pulled the one bad card.
他们认为...他们必须得在日出前杀了你
They think... They think they have to kill you before sunrise.
-你说什么  -跟我来
- What the fuck? - Follow me.
等一下
One sec!
我忘拿枪了
I forgot my gun.
好了
Okay.
你给我听好  不能再搞砸了
Okay, girl, no more fuckups.
你是个赢家  明白吗
You're a winner. You got that?
-你拿上鞋了吗  -亚历克斯
- Okay, you have your shoes? - Alex.
亲爱的  我需要你穿上鞋
Honey, I need you to put on your shoes.
不行  亚历克斯  这他妈是怎么回事
No, Alex, Alex, what the fuck is going on?
我需要你穿上鞋  快穿
I need you to put your shoes on. Right now.
就这样  好的
Okay, here we go. Here we go.
好了
Okay.
他们认为如果他们不杀了你
They think that if they don't kill you,
噩运就会降临整个家族
something very bad will happen to the family.
我必须配合演戏才能把你救出来
Now... I had to play along so that I can get you out.
但是目前整栋房子封锁了
But the house is on lock down right now,
所以要逃出去不太好办
so it's gonna be really tricky.
你本就知道如果我抽到那张牌会发生什么
You knew what would happen if I pulled that card.
我没想到他们会动真格
I didn't think they'd actually go through with it.
你早就知道
You fucking knew!
从未有人抽到那张牌  这情形从未发生过
No one ever pulls that. It never fucking happens.
-但你早就知道有这回事  -我完全没料到
- Yeah, but you knew about it! - No, no, I didn't.
-我是理查德·巴比斯  -我是查理
- I'm Richard Babis. - And I'm Charlie.
今天的主题叫作
And today's segment is called
"认识你的弩弓"
"Getting to know your crossbow."
该死  我真的...以为不会出事
Oh, fuck. I really... I thought it was safe.
但如果我不让你抽牌的话  那么...
But if I didn't pull a card at all, then...
那么你的神经病家人就不会试图...
Then your crazy family wouldn't be trying to...
天呐  他们会杀了我的
Oh, my God, they're gonna kill me.
不  那么我俩都会死
No, then we'd both be dead.
嫁入这个家门  就必须玩这个游戏
When you marry into this family you have to play a game.
如果你不玩  你就会死
And if you don't, you die.
我知道这听起来很疯狂
I know that sounds crazy,
但是你必须相信我  这是真的
but you have to believe me, it is real.
我的叔公就因此丧命
It happened to my great-uncle.
他结婚了  没玩游戏  次日清晨他就死了
He got married, he didn't play a game, next morning he died.
他的妻子也死了
His wife too.
同样的事也发生在了我堂姐瑞秋身上
Same thing happened to my cousin Rachel.
以及一群我从未见过的人身上
Same thing happened to a bunch of people that I never even met before.
你只能...
You just...
你必须玩游戏
You have to play.
你说过你的家庭...很操蛋
You said your family was... fucked-up,
-没错  -可你没提过他们是变态杀人魔啊
- I know. - but you didn't say psycho killers.
你...你娶了我进门  却没提醒我
You... you brought me here, you didn't warn me.
是你想结婚的
You wanted to get married.
-所以是我的错吗  -不是  对不起  我错了
- So it's my fucking fault? - No. I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
-你认真的吗  -嘘
- Are you fucking serious? - Shh.
-我们本可以私奔  -我知道
- We could've eloped. - I know.
-我们本可以...  -不行  有规则的
- We could've... - No, no. There are rules.
不能私奔
You can't just elope.
必须在这里举行婚礼
You... you have to have the wedding here,
还得玩那该死的游戏
and you have to play the fucking game.
你都没跟我说
You didn't even fucking talk to me.
你本可以告诉我  我们本可以...
You could've told me. We could've...just...
如果我事先告诉你  你就会离开我
If I told you, you would've left.
如果我不求婚  你也会离开我
And if I didn't propose, you would've left.
你是我的一切  我向你保证
You're everything to me, and I promise you
我会帮你离开这里  好吗
I'm gonna get you out of here, okay?
好吗  听我说
All right? So just listen to me.
你要沿着这条走廊一直走
You just need to go straight down this hallway
直至你走到仆人厨房
until you get to the service kitchen.
我去警卫室
I'm gonna go down to the security room.
我会把所有的门锁都打开
I'm gonna unlock all the doors. I'm gonna unlock all the doors.
-不  你不许离开我  -然后你赶紧逃走
- No. Don't fucking leave me. - Then you just fucking run.
我必须这么做  亲爱的  我没得选
I have to. Honey, I have to.
一直待在过道里  直到你走到厨...
Just... just stay inside the walls until you get to the kit...
你办得到  你要去哪
You can do this. Where you going?
直走  走到厨房
Straight and then, um, kitchen.
走到厨房  很好
To the kitchen. Good. Good.
你会没事的  一切都会没事的
You're gonna make it. It's gonna be okay.
-我爱你  -我也爱你
- I love you. - I love you.
走  快走
Go. Go.
好
Okay.
操
Fuck.
看到她了吗
Any sign of her?
没有  指不定她藏到哪了
No. She could be anywhere.
找到她了
Found her.
我的天
Jesus! Fuck!
该死
Goddammit!
艾米丽  你得瞄准重心打
Emilie, aim for the center of gravity!
我不知道我在干什么
I don't know what I'm doing!
我只是来拿酒喝
I just came to get a drink.
我必须得喊其他人过来
I have to call the others.
不  你不用
No, you don't.
不要
No.
你可以帮我  求你了
You can help me. Please.
你不会有好下场的
This doesn't end well for you.
我只是不想成为那个把你送上祭台的人
I just don't wanna be the one to serve you up.
丹尼尔  我求求你了
Daniel, I'm begging you.
对于这一切我深感抱歉
I'm really sorry about all this.
人们说得对  富人们确实不同
It's true what they say: The rich really are different.
我让你十秒钟
I'll give you a ten-second head start.
丹尼尔
Daniel.
一
One, one thousand.
二
Two, one thousand.
二点五
Two and a half, one thousand.
她在书房里
She's in the study!
不要把武器对准自己
Point the weapon away from you.
你把她跟丢了吗
You lost her?
没错
Indeed.
你太可悲了
You're pathetic.
没错
Indeed.
你能至少假装在乎吗
Could you at least pretend to care?
我相信无论有没有我的帮助
I'm sure you'll find her and kill her
你们都会找到她  并杀了她
with or without my help.
不过我确实想到了一件事
You know, something did occur to me, though.
亚历克斯瞒着格蕾丝也许是错误的
Alex may have been wrong to keep Grace in the dark...
但你还记得当年我告诉你真相时
but do you remember how you reacted
你有什么反应吗
when I told you about this?
你他妈连眼睛都没眨一下
You didn't fucking blink.
你迫不及待地要出卖你的灵魂
I mean, you couldn't wait to sign your soul away.
你知道我的出身
You know where I came from
还有我之前的人生是什么样子
and what my life was like before.
我宁愿死也不想失去这一切
I'd rather be dead than lose all of this.
小心愿望成真
Well... from your lips.
-她在哪里  -恐怕她刚刚跑了
- Where is she? - I'm afraid you just missed her.
托尼  亚历克斯溜出来了  我很抱歉
Tony, Alex got out. I'm so sorry.
该死
Goddammit.
现在是谁不靠谱
Who's the fuckup now, right?
还是我吗
Still me?
找到她了吗  游戏结束了吗
Did you find her? Is it over?
不  还没结束
No, it's not over.
现在她知道这是怎么回事了
And now she knows what's going on.
不过艾米丽朝克莱拉脸上开了一枪
But Emilie shot Clara in the face.
她死了  只是个小插曲
So she's dead. That's just a side note.
克莱拉死了吗
Clara's dead?
我最喜欢她了
She was my favorite.
糟糕  我忘记拿我的枪了
Cock! I forgot my gun.
爸爸  我忘记拿枪了  我太差劲了
Daddy, I forgot my gun. I suck.
-没关系  -我太差劲了
- It's okay. - I suck!
你不差劲  亲爱的
You don't suck, sweetheart.
给你  亲爱的  用我的吧
Here, hon, why don't you just use mine.
勒多马斯先生  我刚看到她跑过去...
Mr. Le Domas, Mr. Le Domas, I just saw her running...
-天啊  -天啊
- Oh, my God! - Oh, my God.
-好吧  -为什么我总是这样
- Okay, now... - Why does this always happen to me?
-够了  -冷静
- Come on! - Okay. Calm down.
宝贝
Baby.
-没事  亲爱的  走吧  -别生气
- Yeah, okay, that's okay, honey. Come on. - Don't be mad.
去散散步  给你弄块大麻点心
Let's go take a walk, find you an edible,
帮你缓缓
even you out a little bit.
让另一个还活着的仆人来收拾一下吧
Maybe we'll find the other one that's still alive to clean that shit up.
等等
So, wait.
仆人算数吗
Does the help count?
不算
No!
为什么大家一直这么问
Why does everyone keep asking that?
我们必须...
We must...
见鬼了
What the fuck!
我们必须在黎明前杀死新娘
We must kill the bride by dawn.
我们完蛋了  彻底完蛋了
We're fucked. I mean, we are so fucked.
冷静点  先解决问题
Calm down. Work the problem.
我们应该用监控摄像头
We should use the security cameras.
你不尊重传统
You have no respect for tradition.
不  她说得对
No, she's right.
要是曾祖父有摄像头
Don't you think Great-Grandfather
难道他不会用吗
would've used the security cameras if he had them?
他在摄像头问世前出生又不是传统
I mean, it's not tradition that he was born before cameras.
这太愚蠢了
That's... that's stupid.
没错
Exactly.
时代改变了
Times change.
说起这个  我能用本世纪制造的武器吗
Speaking of which, may I please use a weapon made this century?
-我的包里有一把枪  -是吗
- I have a gun in my purse. - You do?
不  不  我们得用曾祖父的武器
No. No. We use Great-Grandfather's.
这是传统
That's tradition.
你们总是挑来拣去
You pick and choose. Pick and choose.
至少你没让我们戴那些愚蠢的面具
At least you're not making us wear those fucking masks.
没错  那是爸爸的主意
Oh, no. That was Dad's idea.
八十年代的风格
It was the '80s.
-必须保持对传统的敬畏  -够了  姐姐
- Our reverence must not wane. - Goddammit, Sis!
我们要是不找到她
If we don't find her
在黎明前举行仪式  我们都会死
and perform the ritual before dawn, we're all dead.
托尼  带上丹尼尔去打开摄像头
Tony, take Daniel and turn on the cameras.
其他人分头行动  找找亚历克斯
Everyone else fan out, and somebody find Alex.
天啊
Jesus.
操  操
Fucking shit. Fuck.
快  亚历克斯
Come on, Alex.
监控  监控
Monitors. Monitors.
好了
Okay.
糟糕
Oh, shit.
靠  靠  靠  靠
Shit, shit, shit, shit.
你姑姑总是执着于细节
Your aunt always gets lost in the details.
谁在乎我们怎么找到她
Who gives a shit how we find her?
我完全同意
I agree completely.
-看来不止是我们这么想  -什么
- Looks like we're not the only ones. - What?
有人打开摄像头了
Someone turned on the cameras.
是亚历克斯
Alex.
开门  快开门
Open doors. Open fucking doors.
我操
Oh, fuck.
让开
Move.
恐怕我做不到
I'm afraid I can't do that.
那些弹药只是展品
The ammunition is display only.
你以为我真的那么愚蠢...
Now, did you really think I would be stupid enough to...
干得好
Fuck yeah!
开门  亚历克斯
Open the door, Alex!
她在这里
She's in here!
快他妈开门
Open the goddamn door!
该死  亚历克斯
Goddammit, Alex!
开门
Open this door!
不  不
No, no. Hey, no!
你要是不帮我们  就滚蛋
If you're not gonna help us, get the hell out.
你他妈别伤害她
You fucking leave her alone!
明白了吗
You understand me?
-亚历克斯  -她是我妻子
- Alex! - That's my wife!
亚历克斯
Alex.
亚历克斯  你不必这么做
Alex, you don't have to do this.
亚历克斯
Alex.
好
Okay.
天啊  天啊
Oh, God. Oh, God.
我明白
I know, I know.
-我明白  -你得帮我  你得帮我
- I know. - You gotta help me. You gotta help me.
-她是我的一切  -我明白
- She's everything to me. - I know.
我们会救她出去
We'll get her out.
-谢谢你  拜托  -我保证
- Okay, thank you. Please. - I promise.
你是哪边的
Whose side are you on?
我分散了他的注意力  不是吗
I distracted him, didn't I?
选吧
Call it.
谁他妈在乎
Fucking who cares?
反面  你搬头
Tails. You take the head.
该死
Goddammit.
-等等  我得拿上我的枪  -回来再拿吧
- Wait, wait. I gotta get my gun. - Just come back for it.
快点
Move your ass!
我搬的部分比较重  父亲
I'm carrying the heavy part, Father.
多年的酗酒和吸毒已经造成了苦果
Years of alcohol and drug abuse have taken a toll.
-天啊  -天啊
- Oh, my God. - Oh, my God.
-我不明白是怎么回事  -没事
- I don't understand what's going on. - Okay. Okay.
你要保持安静  好吗
I need you to be quiet, okay?
我根本不是女仆
Look, I'm not even a maid.
勒多马斯先生只是喜欢我的舞姿
Mr. Le Domas, he just likes the way I dance.
我们换一下位置
Okay, let's swap places.
他们在找我  不是找你
Yeah, cause they're looking for me, they're not looking for you.
快  快
So, come on. Come on.
-拜托  -她在这里
- Please. - She's over here!
-她在这里  在这里  -不  不
- She's here! She's over here! - No, no, no, no.
天啊  天啊
Oh, my God. Oh, my God.
救我  拜托
Help me, please.
-靠  -拜托
- Shit. - Please.
靠
Shit.
托尼
Tony.
你在干什么
What are you doing?
我们想让他回归家族
We're trying to bring him back to us.
先生
Sir.
天啊
Oh, man.
我没能修复安全系统
I was unable to repair the security system.
门窗现在都开着
The doors and windows remain unlocked.
恐怕多拉被压扁了  先生
And I'm afraid that Dora has been crushed, sir.
在升降机里
By the dumbwaiter.
《无人生还》是著名英国推理小说作家
阿加莎·克里斯蒂的名作
无人生还
And then there were none.
老天啊
Jesus Christ.
她要干掉我们所有人
She's taking us all out.
-她是怎么做到的  -亲爱的
- How's she doing this? - Sweetheart.
这没道理  贝基
It doesn't make sense, Becky.
-她只是个金发小妞  我不...  -托尼
- She's a little blonde twig, and I don't... - Tony.
你休息一会儿
Take a minute.
就一小会儿
But just a minute.
我们不能让她跑出去  我们得守住门
We can't let her get out. We've got to guard the doors.
他迷失了自我
He lost his way.
你根本不应该让他离开我们
You should never have let him leave us.
你说什么
Excuse me?
他和我一直都很相似
He and I have always been so much alike.
我知道那姑娘会抽出那张牌
I knew the girl would draw that card,
他会面临和我一样的选择
and that he would face the same choice I faced.
鬼扯
Horse shit.
没人料得到今晚会这样
None of us expected to be doing this tonight.
我早上八点还要打高尔夫呢
I got a tee time at eight.
而且你可能没注意到
And, in case you didn't notice,
这对他来说根本算不上选择
it wasn't much of a choice for him.
他一开始就在帮她
He's been helping her from the get-go.
-他恨我们  -不
- He hates us. - No.
他只是害怕真实的自己
He's simply afraid of who he truly is.
如同我过去一样
Like I was.
你根本想象不出那天晚上
You'll never know how it felt that night
我得知我唯一爱过的男人必须死的感受
to be told that the only man that I'd ever loved had to die.
但我不应该反抗的
But I should not have fought it.
我应该亲手杀了查尔斯的
I should have killed Charles myself.
亚历克斯还来得及做正确的事
There's still time for Alex to do the right thing.
他只需要接受真相
He only has to accept the truth.
什么真相
What truth is that?
他生来是为了领导家族  而非逃离家族
That he is meant to lead this family, not run from it.
他一开始就讨厌我们的契约
He's hated our pact from the very start.
他是有良心的那个儿子  你还记得吗
He's the good son. Do you remember that?
那为什么我们中只有他
Then why is he the only one of us
见过椅子上坐的勒贝尔先生
who has ever seen Mr. Le Bail in his chair?
天呐  他当时才五岁
Good God. He was five.
他可能是做梦梦到的
He was probably, I don't know, dreaming it.
或者是编的
Or maybe he made it up.
你非这么说也行
Well, if you say so.
搜索
恶魔契约是真的还是胡扯
来自基普的新信息
干什么呢  老铁
"干什么呢  老铁"
"What up, dawg?"
蠢货
Idiot.
没什么  家务事
没什么
Not much.
家务事
Family shit.
乔治
Georgie?
感谢老天  好
Oh, thank God. Okay.
好  我知道这真的非常非常吓人
Okay, listen, I know this is really, really scary, but...
操
Fuck.
见鬼
Shit.
操
Fuck.
你这小混蛋
You little fucker!
我逮住你了
I got you.
我逮住你了  贱人
I got you, bitch.
操
Fuck!
她在外面  正在跑向北边的栅栏
She's outside, running towards the north fence.
我去找其他人
I'll get the others.
救命
Help me!
救救我
Please help!
救命  救救我
Help. Please help me.
救命
Help!
操  操  操
Fuck. Fuck. Fuck.
救命  等等  停车
Help! Wait, stop.
救救我
Please, please help me.
谢天谢地  谢谢  谢谢
Oh, thank God. Thank you, thank you.
-从路上滚开  -等一下
- Get the fuck out of the road. - Please wait.
你他妈什么毛病
What the fuck is wrong with you?
你这禽兽
You fucking animal.
你这混蛋  人渣
You piece of shit, little, tiny dick-licker,
败类  操
fucking asshole, fucking I...
该死的有钱人
Fucking rich people.
操
Fuck.
她肯定是逃进林子里去了
She must've gone into the woods.
不过别担心  先生  她跑不远
But don't worry, sir, she won't get far.
我会找到她的
I'll find her.
明天我就会修好栅栏
And I'll fix the fence tomorrow.
好吧
Well...
她出去了
she's out.
今晚很尽兴
This was fun.
怎么样
What do you say we, uh,
我们明天早午餐时平分掉贺礼如何
divvy up the wedding gifts at brunch tomorrow?
你以为这是玩游戏吗
Do you think that this is a fucking game?
对啊
Yes.
还记得这是捉迷藏吗
Hide and seek, remember?
你知道要是她活到黎明
Do you realize that if she lives till dawn,
我们都得死吗
that we're all gonna die?
你们都还记得范霍恩一家的下场吧
You all remember what happened to the Van Horns, right?
他们不是死于房屋起火吗
Didn't they just die in a house fire?
新闻是这么报道的  但他们...
Yeah, that's what the press told you, but they...
你不会想知道他们实际上怎么死的  相信我
You don't wanna know how they really died. Trust me.
可不能得罪勒贝尔先生
No, you don't fuck Mr. Le Bail.
否则勒贝尔先生会让你好看
Mr. Le Bail fucks you.
你就不能协商个更好的契约吗  维克
You couldn't have negotiated better terms, huh, Vic?
你就不能
You couldn't have, uh...
比方说  砍砍价
I don't know, maybe talked him down
砍掉整个屠杀条款吗
on the whole eradication clause?
这都怪你  混球
Well, here's to you, fucker,
因为我们现在大事不好了
because now we are all fucking fucked!
你已经说清楚了  亲爱的  谢谢
I think you made your point, sweetheart, thank you.
真他妈的
Holy dick.
去等斯蒂文斯  他可能需要你们帮忙
Go wait for Stevens. He might need your help.
不是你们俩  你们别碍事
Not you two. I want you out of the way.
把女仆的尸体运到羊圈去
Take the maids to the goat pit.
还有  甜心  尽量别杀人了
And, pumpkin, try not to kill anyone else.
败类负责清洁工作
Cleanup duty for the fuckups.
-不  爸爸  -去吧  小艾
- No. Daddy. - Come on, Em.
听你妈妈的
Listen to your mother.
我们什么时候溜之大吉
So, at what point do we just cut and run?
是吧
Right?
拜托  是吧
I mean, come on. Right?
去死
Fuck you.
丹尼尔
Daniel!
丹尼尔  帮帮我
Daniel, help!
格蕾丝
Grace.
她为什么非得抽出"捉迷藏"
Why did she have to pull "Hide and seek"?
你说这是真的吗
Do you think it's real?
什么  是说我们不杀了她
What? That we'll implode
就会自爆或者自燃而死之类的吗
or burst into flames, or whatever, if we don't kill her?
我不知道  你能...
I don't know. Can you...
行  我来
All right, I'll...
-我需要  我需要你帮我  -不行  你吐的话我也会吐
- I need, I need you to... - I can't. If you barf, I'll barf.
一  二  三
One, two, three.
三
Three.
但是上次他们玩捉迷藏时
But you were with them
你也和他们一起玩了  是不是
the last time they played hide and seek, weren't you?
你当时是六岁还是七岁
Were you six, seven?
你还记得什么吗
Do you remember anything?
我记得一清二楚
I remember all of it.
亚历克斯当时也在
Alex was with me too.
我尽力保护他了
I tried to protect him.
我不知道他看见或者记住了什么
I don't know what he saw or what he remembers.
你总是照顾他
You always looked out for him.
要是那样  我就不会让他娶格蕾丝
If that were true, I wouldn't have let him marry Grace.
他值得更好的兄弟
He deserved a better brother.
而我们都该死
And we all deserve to die.
我的孩子们不该死
My kids don't.
妈妈
Mommy?
宝贝  乔治
Honey! Georgie.
你还好吗  你在外面做什么
Are you okay? What are you doing out here?
我...
I...
我跟着那位女士过来的
I followed that lady down here,
然后用我找到的枪击中了她
and I shot her with that gun I found.
你为什么那么做
Why would you do that?
大家都是那么做的
That's what everyone else was trying to do.
宝贝
Sweetie.
我真为你骄傲
I am so proud of you.
见鬼
Shit.
过来  格蕾丝
Come here, Grace!
该死的混账
Fucking asshole!
你这混蛋
You motherfucker.
感谢你拨打出行安全热线
Thank you for calling Trip Safe.
请保持通话  我们将为你接通
Please stay on the line and you'll be connected
下一个有空的代表
to the next available representative.
晚上好  我是贾斯汀  你的通话可能被录音...
Good evening. This is Justin. Your call may be monitored...
有人要杀我  你能帮帮我吗
People are trying to kill me. Can you please help me?
好的  我可以帮你
Yes, I can help you with that.
你需要医疗帮助还是...
Do you need medical assistance, or...
你能报警吗
Can you call the police, please?
好的  我很乐意帮你
Yes. I'd be happy to help you with that.
抱歉  电脑又出故障了
Sorry. The computer's acting up again.
我马上重启
Let me just quickly reboot here.
贾斯汀  快他妈报警
Justin, just call the fucking police.
女士  这边显示这辆车被报失窃了
Ma'am, it says here that the car was reported stolen.
对不起  但我必须把车停下
I'm sorry, but I have to shut it down.
不  什么
No, what?
不  搞什么  你他妈在开玩笑吗
No, what the fuck? Are you fucking kidding me?
这是公司的规定  女士
It's company policy, ma'am.
-我无能为力  -不  不  求你了  贾斯汀
- There's nothing I can do. - No, no, no, please. Justin.
待在车里  女士  警察在路上了
Just stay with the vehicle, ma'am. Police are on their way.
快他妈启动啊
Just start the fucking car!
-好吧  不必飙脏话  -快启动  贾斯汀
- 'Kay, there's no need for profanity. - Start the car, Justin!
天啊  我也无能为力  束手无策
Jesus, there's nothing I can do. My hands are tied.
贾斯汀
Justin.
喂  贾斯汀
Hello? Justin!
还有什么我可以帮你的吗
Is there anything else I can help you with?
有  你吃屎去吧  贾斯汀
Yeah, you can go fuck yourself, Justin!
好吧  感谢拨打出行安全热线  祝你晚安
Okay. Thanks for using Trip Safe. Have a great night.
好吧  没事  没事  没事
Okay. You're okay, you're okay, you're okay.
警察在路上了
Police are on the way.
警察在路上了  一切都会...
Police are on their way. Everything's gonna be...
晚安  格蕾丝
Good night, Grace.
亚历克斯  是你吗
Alex, is that you?
你现在安全了
Hey, you're safe now.
我们要走了
We're leaving.
你们在哪
Where are you?
我们要到后门了  先生
We're approaching the rear gate, sir.
我们马上就到
We'll be there shortly.
好  回到正题
All right. We are back in business.
托尼
Tony.
斯蒂文斯  小心后面
Hey, Stevens! Look behind you.
斯蒂文斯
Stevens!
音乐开小声点  白痴
Turn down the fucking music, you idiot!
不
Oh, no.
通话中断
见鬼
Oh, fuck.
操
Fuck!
似曾相识啊
Déjà vu.
有意思  我来这里是为了逃避疯狂
It's funny, I... came out here to escape the madness.
感谢用一场车祸打扰我的宁静
Thanks for crashing a car into my tranquility.
丹尼尔
Daniel.
你并不想杀我  你不想让我死
You don't wanna kill me. You don't want me to die.
对  我不想
No, I don't.
我喜欢你  格蕾丝
I like you, Grace.
那就放我走  好吗
So let me go. Okay?
我没骨气
I'm weak.
你是个好人
You're a good guy.
你真的是个大好人
You're a really, really, really good guy.
还有亚历克斯  亚历克斯爱你
And Alex, Alex loves you.
你也爱他
And you love him.
你要是动手了  他不会原谅你的
He's not gonna forgive you if you do this.
或许是吧
Maybe not.
但至少他能活下来
But at least he'll be alive.
我不能让我全家人因为你而死掉
I can't let my entire family die because of you.
真是疯了
It's insane.
你没意识到这有多荒唐吗
Can't you see it's insane?
谁都不会死  谁都不会  都不会死
No one's gonna die... No one, no one is gonna die.
而你可以做些什么
And you can do something about it.
那都是胡扯
It's bullshit!
不
No.
我不是你想象的那样
I am not who you think I am.
亚历克斯才是脱身的那个人
Alex is the one who got out.
能救你的也只有他
If anyone was gonna save you, it would've been him.
现在你可以出来了
You can come out now.
怎么  你知道我在这
What, you knew I was here?
我醉了  又没瞎
I'm drunk, I'm not blind.
我们得快点了  还有不到一小时就黎明了
We gotta move. Less than an hour till dawn.
我们还得给她为仪式做好准备
And we still need to prepare her for the ritual.
格蕾丝在哪
Where's Grace?
她身体不适
She's indisposed.
你不会真以为我会坐视不理吧
You didn't think I was just gonna let it happen, did you?
对于家人  只能保持乐观
With family, one hopes for the best.
问题是
The thing is...
我喜欢她
I like her.
我不想这么做
I don't wanna do this.
但我们必须保护家族
But we have to protect the family.
如果她死了
If she dies...
我会杀了你
I'll kill you.
好吧
Well...
那看来我难逃一死了
then I suppose I'm dead either way.
是  或许那都是胡说八道  什么都不会发生
Yeah, and maybe it's a crock of shit and nothing will happen.
别闹了
Oh, please.
如果你真这么想
If you believed that,
你根本就不会让她去抽牌
you wouldn't have let her draw a card at all.
你为什么离开我们  亚历克斯
Why did you leave us, Alex?
我不知道  妈
I don't know, Mom.
我不知道  或许是在某个晚上
I don't know. Maybe one night when I was
我念着咒语给羊割喉的时候
chanting and slicing the throat of a goat,
突然意识到这么做不太正常吧
it occurred to me that that wasn't a completely normal thing to do.
但这才是最让我害怕的
But, and this is what scared me the most...
曾经感觉是正常的
it felt normal.
确实是
It did.
然后我意识到如果家人说没关系
And I realized that you'll do pretty much anything...
那你什么事都能做得出来
if your family says it's okay.
然后我遇到了格蕾丝
And then I met Grace.
她与你们所有人截然相反
She's the opposite of all of you.
她是好人
She's good.
她让我觉得我也可以变好
And she made me feel like I could be good too.
所以如果在你们和她之间选
So, if it comes down to you or her,
我会选她
I choose her.
我不信你说的话
I don't believe you.
我觉得你也不相信
And I don't think that you believe
一个你才认识一年半的女孩
that a girl that you've known for a year and a half...
会比我更了解你
knows you better than I do.
我们家有个很特别的朋友  勒贝尔先生
Our family has a very special friend named Mr. Le Bail.
勒贝尔先生让我们拥有了今天这一切美好的事物
Mr. Le Bail is the reason we have all the nice things we have.
但勒贝尔先生有时也需要我们的回报
But sometimes Mr. Le Bail wants something from us in return.
你可以的  菲奇
You got this, Fitch.
You got this, Fitch!
别怂  菲奇
Don't be a bitch, Fitch.
你可以的  怂炮
You got this, bitch.
我知道今晚没有按计划进行
I know tonight didn't go as planned.
但我会弥补的  勒贝尔先生
But I'll make it right, Mr. Le Bail.
请拭目以待
You'll see.
我们今晚在祖先面前
We renew our pledge this night,
献上鲜活的血肉
as our ancestors before us...
重新宣誓
with this offering of living flesh and blood.
万岁
Hail...
弟弟
Brother!
有毒
Poisoned!
你这个混蛋
You son of a bitch!
天啊
Oh, God.
你给我们喝了什么
What did you give us?
我们在女仆们身上倒的东西
Stuff we poured on the maids.
白瓶子  红瓶盖
White bottle, little red cap.
盐酸
Hydrochloric acid!
快  赶紧走
Come on, up and at 'em.
格蕾丝
Grace!
-你...你是把他们杀了吗  -没有  只加了一点
- Did you... Did you just kill 'em? - No, I just gave them a nip.
我上网查过  他们只会闹一周肚子  没事的
I Googled it. They'll shit weird for a week, but they'll be fine.
-别担心  我也会让亚历克斯脱身的  -去找他们
- Don't worry, I'll get Alex out too. - Find them!
我们不必...
We don't have...
我就知道你会帮我
I knew you'd help me.
我没有
I didn't.
我只知道  得有人出来断了这个传统
All I knew was, at some point, somebody had to burn it all down.
从未想到会是我
Never thought it'd be me.
丹尼尔
Daniel.
让开
Get out of the way.
夏丽蒂
Charity.
你真的不在乎我会不会死
You really don't care if I die.
你不必...
You don't have to...
丹尼尔  丹尼尔  丹尼尔
Daniel. Daniel. Daniel.
快走
Go.
谢谢你
Thank you.
你想去哪啊  贱人
Where do you think you're going, bitch?
你他妈以为你是谁
Who the fuck do you think you are?
我们家经受过比你更糟的事
Our family's weathered worse than you.
你不过是又一个祭品
You're just another sacrifice.
又一只羊
You're another goat.
去他的祭坛
Fuck the altar.
我就在这里动手
I'm gonna do it right here.
格蕾丝
Grace?
丹尼尔  丹尼尔  丹尼尔
Daniel. Daniel. Daniel.
看着我  天啊  看着我
Look at me. Oh, my God. Look at me.
我得辩解一下  有一阵没练过了
In my defense, it's been a while.
别死  别死
Don't go. Don't go, okay?
丹尼尔  别死  我需要你  别死
Daniel, don't go! Don't go! I need you, Daniel! Don't go!
我今早说的话是认真的
I meant what I said this morning.
我还以为你会成为新的我
I thought you were gonna be the new me.
但我不会让你害了我家
But I'm not gonna let you hurt my family!
你可以去死了
You can die.
你根本不配有家
You don't deserve a family.
谁要你们家
Fuck your family.
你们家去死吧
Fuck your fucking family!
格蕾丝
Grace.
我很抱歉
I'm sorry.
抱歉
我也很抱歉
Yeah, I'm sorry too.
丹尼尔死了
Daniel's dead.
这之后你不会和我在一起了  对不对
You won't be with me after this, will you?
亚历克斯
Alex...
Alex.
亚历克斯
-你弄疼我了  -她在这里
- You're hurting me. - She's in here!
不  求你了  不要
No, please, no, no!
不要
Please!
放开我
Let me go!
好样的
Attaboy.
贝基
Becky.
马上就要日出了  我们必须现在动手
The sun is about to rise! We must do it now!
你的两个儿子该加入我们了
It is time for your boys to take their place.
伟大的主  救我们脱离过去的错误和妄想
Deliver us, O mighty one, from all past error and delusion.
我们踏上了黑暗之路
That, having set our foot upon the path of darkness,
我们的决心不会动摇
we may not weaken in our resolve.
但有您的帮助  智慧和力量就会成长
But, with thy assistance, grow in wisdom and strength.
撒旦万岁
Hail Satan!
Hail Satan.
撒旦万岁
不
No.
游戏输了
It is lost.
原谅我们
Forgive us.
什么也没发生
Nothing's happening.
我就知道
I knew it.
我就知道  全是胡说八道
I fucking knew it. It's all bullshit.
格蕾丝
Grace.
那...
So, what...
我们怎么处理她
What should we do about her?
我知道太迟了
I know it is too late.
但我不会再让你失望了
But I will not fail you again.
这女孩还是要死
The girl still dies!
什么鬼
What the fuck?
谁想玩个游戏
Who wants to play a game?
该玩捉迷藏啦
It's time for hide and seek.
♪ 跑  跑  跑 ♪
♪ Run, run, run ♪
♪ 跑去藏起来 ♪
♪ Time to run and hide ♪
♪ 跑  跑  跑 ♪
♪ Run, run, run ♪
操
Fuck.
♪ 我会找到你 ♪
♪ And now I'm going to find you ♪
我想你是对的
I think you were right.
♪ 你逃进黑暗中 ♪
♪ You scurry off into the darkness ♪
♪ 快呀  我在你身后 ♪
♪ Hurry, I'm behind you ♪
勒贝尔先生  我收回那句话
Mr. Le Bail, I take it back.
♪ 别  出  声 ♪
♪ Don't you speak ♪
我想回家
I wanna go home.
♪ 捉  迷  藏 ♪
♪ Hide and seek ♪
操
Fuck!
躲起来  躲起来
Hide! Hide!
♪ 溜进地窖 ♪
♪ Tiptoe to the cellar ♪
♪ 或者爬进床底 ♪
♪ Or crawl under your bed ♪
♪ 无论你逃到哪里 ♪
♪ Anywhere you've fled ♪
♪ 我会找到你 ♪
♪ I am going to find you ♪
♪ 躲进阴影里 ♪
♪ Stay inside the shadows ♪
♪ 男孩女孩们 ♪
♪ All you girls and boys ♪
♪ 千万别出声 ♪
♪ Don't you make a noise ♪
不  我每件事都做对了
No! I did everything right.
♪ 不然我会找到你 ♪
♪ Or I am going to find you ♪
♪ 跑  跑  跑 ♪
♪ Run, run, run ♪
我按规则玩了
I played by the rules.
♪ 悄悄靠近猎物 ♪
♪ Creep up on my prey ♪
一切在我掌控之...
And I'm in control...
♪ 跑  跑  跑 ♪
♪ Run, run, run ♪
♪ 夜晚悄悄溜走 ♪
♪ Stalk the night away ♪
♪ 你可以跑进夜色 ♪
♪ You can scuttle off into the night ♪
♪ 但你身后会是谁 ♪
♪ But what will be behind you ♪
♪ 别  出  声 ♪
♪ Don't you speak ♪
♪ 捉  迷  藏 ♪
♪ Hide and seek... ♪
不  别走
No, don't leave.
别离开我  亲爱的  我真的很抱歉
Don't leave me, honey. Honey, I'm really sorry.
-我不想死  -我也不想  你个自私鬼
- I don't wanna die. But... - Neither did I, you selfish fuck.
不  我和他们不一样  不一样
No, I'm not like them. I'm not like them.
♪ 滴  滴  答 ♪
♪ Tick, tick, tock ♪
我和他们不一样  你让我变得更好  亲爱的
I'm not like them. No, you made me better, honey.
而且他没要我的命
And he's not taking me.
♪ 快跑进黑暗中 ♪
♪ Hasten off into the black ♪
对吧
Right?
我有重来的机会  亲爱的
I get a do-over, sweetie.
都是因为你  对吧  亲爱的
And that's because of you. Yeah? Sweetie?
格蕾丝  我真的很害怕
Grace, I'm really scared.
别他妈碰我
Don't fucking touch me.
好  不碰
No, okay.
♪ 十  九  八 ♪
♪ Ten, nine, eight ♪
亚历克斯
Alex.
♪ 七  六 ♪
♪ Seven, six ♪
什么
Yeah?
♪ 五 ♪
♪ Five ♪
♪ 四  三 ♪
♪ Four, three ♪
我要离婚
I want a divorce
♪ 二 ♪
♪ Two ♪
♪ 一 ♪
♪ One ♪
操
Fuck.
家族仪式  秘密议会  勒贝尔的险招
日出  急急如律令
勒贝尔的险招
Love Me Tender
♪ 温柔爱我  甜蜜爱我 ♪
♪ Love me tender, love me sweet ♪
♪ 绝不放开我的手 ♪
♪ Never let me go ♪
♪ 你完整了我的人生 ♪
♪ You have made my life complete ♪
♪ 我是那么爱你 ♪
♪ And I love you so ♪
♪ 温柔爱我  真心爱我 ♪
♪ Love me tender, love me true ♪
♪ 我所有梦想圆满 ♪
♪ All my dreams fulfill ♪
♪ 因为亲爱的  我爱你 ♪
♪ For, my darling I love you ♪
♪ 永永远远爱你 ♪
♪ And I always will ♪
♪ 温柔爱我  长久爱我 ♪
♪ Love me tender, love me long ♪
♪ 把我放在你心中 ♪
♪ Take me to your heart ♪
♪ 因为那里是我的归属 ♪
♪ For it's there that I belong ♪
♪ 永远不会离去 ♪
♪ And will never part ♪
♪ 温柔爱我  真心爱我 ♪
♪ Love me tender and love me true ♪
女士  你没事吧
Ma'am, are you okay?
能听到吗
Can you hear me?
♪ 我所有梦想圆满 ♪
♪ All my dreams fulfill ♪
南边草坪上有一个人
I've got someone on the south lawn.
立刻让急救人员过来
We need paramedics over here right away.
♪ 因为亲爱的  我爱你 ♪
♪ For, my darling I love you ♪
收到
Copy that.
老天  你碰上什么事了
Jesus Christ, what happened to you?
♪ 永永远远爱你 ♪
♪ And I always will ♪
亲家
In-laws.